Oh, going to Cuba. I went to Cuba on Prohibition time, too, and I bought a lot of fancy bottles,
like one drink in for souvenirs for all my friends.
Well, Atlantic City, the ship was stopped. It was all in the newspapers about it, too.
The crew had ripped the walls and put all liquor in the walls.
So we all had to get up at three o'clock in the morning.
And, oh, it was a scream. The men were coming down their pajamas and bathrobes,
and they had bottles sticking all out all over, and anyone could see they had the bottles.
And, oh, the captain says, get rid of that stuff.
They're searching the boats. They're downstairs ripping the wall apart.
So...
They looked us all over for liquor and for bringing things in from Cuba.
And the girl in front of me, she had a bottle she was bringing in from her mother-in-law,
and they found that bottle in her bag.
So they found her $50 and threw it over the side of the boat.
So then I got panicky.
I had about six little bottles, and I thought,
I'll have to stay on boat and wash the dishes.
I spent all my money down there.
I was coming home broke.
So the doctors are not allowed to touch the women.
They send you down to the matron.
So when he went to examine me,
he said,
you're a very sick woman, you better go down to the matron.
I was so nervous and upset that my pulse was going so fast. And I couldn't talk. And I was holding my coat around my stomach, see, so they wouldn't...
And I guess he thought I was pregnant, see, because the bottles all started to move to the front.
So he says, oh, like a sick woman, you better go down to the matron. And all I kept thinking about was, oh, if they ever find those bottles, I'll have to stay on ship a month to pay up for it.
If they find you $50 a bottle. I think I had eight. And I was broke because I'd been down there a month and I'd spent my money.
And she didn't examine me. She said, what's the matter? Oh, I said, I'm so nervous. I said, don't worry.
Those doctors, they're fooling around. I said, my friend in front, they threw the bottle overboard, and I got all nervous and upset.
And she says, well, I'll give you a pill and you calm down.
But I would never bring liquor in again after that. I wouldn't go through that again. For no souvenirs.